International Union of Electrical Workers, Local 0485 Records WAG 137
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
International Union of Electrical Workers, Local 0485 Records
undated
WAG 137
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
5.5 linear feet (6 boxes)
Scope and Contents note
INVENTORY AVAILABLE IN REPOSITORY; CONTACT: peter.filardo@nyu.edu.
- Series I: Minutes
  - Stewards Council, Executive Board, and Membership Meetings, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stewards Council, Executive Board, and Membership Meetings, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Membership Meetings, 1958-1960 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board, 1957-1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board and Shop Chairman, 1969-1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Series II: General Files
  - Activities Bulletin, 1957-1960 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Allen Co., 1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Amalgamated Locals, 1958-1962 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Archer, Hamilton, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Badillo, Herman, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Briggs, Ernest, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Cameron, Clifton, 1958-1961 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Classes, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Committees (list), 1961 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Constitution, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Convention, 1956, 1958, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Convention, 1963, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Convention, 1969, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Credit Union, 1956-1960 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Cutroneo, Leo, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Dances, 1953-1963 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Delegates Manual (Spanish), 1953 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Dynamos, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Elections, 1956-1966 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Elections, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Elections, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Elections, 1971, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Elections (UER and MWA), 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Employers (research), 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Eton Silver, inc, 1958-1976 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Executive Committee Report, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Fay, Charles, 1942-1969 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Financial Reports, 1956-1959 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Financial Reports, 1960-1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Financial Reports, 1965-1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Financial Reports, 1970-1977 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Form Letters, 1966-1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Health and Welfare Fund, 1959-1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Human Rights/Civil Rights, 1940-1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Internal Security: Investigations, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Investigation Committee, 1967-1970 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - International Union of Electrical Workers, 1956-1973 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - International Union of Electrical Workers, District 3, 1963-1983 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - International Union of Electrical Workers, District 4, 1956-1963 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - International Union of Electrical Workers, District 4: Defection from Union of Electrical Workers, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - International Union of Electrical Workers, Local 133, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - International Union of Electrical Workers, Local 450, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Jamco Manufacturing Corp., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Jayar Metal Finishing Corp., 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Job Calls, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Job Descriptions, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Job Descriptions (I), 1946-1957 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Job Descriptions (II), 1946-1957 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Labor Council for Latin American Advancement, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Leaflets, 1967-1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Legislative/Political, 1957-1973 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Manley, Nat: Spanish Lessons, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - March on Washington, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Membership Meetings, 1959-1966 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Mineworkers, Support for, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Model Clauses and Contracts, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Nigris, Mike, 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - National Labor Relations Board Cases, 1967-1975 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Parades, 1959-1961 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - "Party" Document (CP?), undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Play: "A Local Grows in Brooklyn", 1960 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Powell, Adam Clayton, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Romans, Angel, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Salguero, Joe, 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Seniority Rosters, 1940-1957 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Shop Meetings, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Shop Newspapers, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Simplex Equipment Shop, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Skilled Trades, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Songs/Poems, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Sperry Locals (Local 450), 1957 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Sperry Strike, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Staff, 1957-1963 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Stagg Zipper Corp., 1964-1975 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Stewards Meetings, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Supreme Court Case: Joseph Markovits, inc., 1957 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Torres, Santiago, 1970-1986 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Tubular Cast, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Tung-Sol Workers, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - United Electrical Workers, 1946-1957 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - United Electrical Workers, Local 475, 1939-1955 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - United Electrical Workers, Local 475: Anti-Discrimination, 1953-1955 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - United Electrical Workers: Till Murder Case, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Yauco Civic and Social Club, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Series III: Bargaining Files
  - Acme Brass, 1968-1973 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Aerosol Machine Corp, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 2)